Mohammad Shahriari

moh.shah96@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/mohshah portfolio: mohshah96.github.io



A unity game developer with the experience of being lead in technical teams, passionate about the code architecture to achieve a readable, maintainable, and extendable code base. I always try to learn more and expand my knowledge. I like to bring unique and joyful experiences to players.

I am interested in procedural generation and complex systems.

I enjoy every video game that feels good to me in any genre. But if I want to name some of them, they are Rogue-Like, Metroidvania, and MOBA.

EXPERIENCE

SEP 2020 - PRESENT

SENIOR GAME DEVELOPER, MEDRICK FZE

- Technical lead of Rooster Wars 2 project (an online strategy game), developing its core game mechanics and designing its overall architecture.
- Participating in the architectural design and developing the in-house infrastructure of a "Live Ops System".
- Tech-lead of "Hokm" project (a multiplayer card game) with the responsibility to maintain and extend it with constant updates.
- Implementing social features like chat, groups, friends, and tournament in "Golshifteh" (a match-3 game with decoration meta), and also preparing its iOS build.
- Tech-lead of "BabaShah" and "Heshmat" projects (same gameplay with different meta) to maintain and extend them with new features, after their main developer left the studio

MAY 2019 - JULY 2021

BACK-END DEVELOPER, PART GAMES STUDIO

- Developing the backend for profile management, purchase verification and matchmaking for our beloved real-time pvp game called "Battle Arena".
- Developing a server application for profile management, leaderboard, chat and purchase verification for our idle-clicker game called "King Keyvan", using .Net Core and MongoDB.
- Developing a socket-based server app for a real-time strategy/tycoon game for a 2-days event called "Game In" at Sharif University of Technology.

MAY 2018 - MAY 2019

UNITY DEVELOPER, PART GAMES STUDIO

- Developing a story-driven point and click adventure game for mobile platforms called "Lost Days".
- Participating in the client side and implementing the socket-based server for a real-time multiplayer strategy/tycoon game.
- Participating in the development of a project which was called "mini games", including about 10 different mini-game as an android application.

• participating in the development of an application for parents to help them with their kids health-related subjects, called "Nikoo".

NOVEMBER 2017 – MAY 2018

GAME DESIGNER, TEETOTUM

I was the designer of a F2P game called "Sick Mind".

- Designing more than 100 puzzle levels in many types like trivia, lateral thinking, spatial reasoning, ...
- Writing a complete GDD for the game.
- Participating in the design of the economy system of the game.
- Managing publish phase including app store screenshot designs and description.

EDUCATION

OCTOBER 2014 – JANUARY 2019

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING, ISLAMIC AZAD UNIVERSITY, CENTRAL TEHRAN BRANCH

SKILLS

- Software Engineering
- C#
- Network programming

- Unity
- Game Maker
- Agile / Scrum
- Git